<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>English-learnings on ByteGopher</title>
    <link>https://airren.github.io/english-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in English-learnings on ByteGopher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://airren.github.io/english-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-13/</guid>
      <description>13th May 2022 Hi, June, this class, I hope you could help me to correct the typo and grammar and make the sentence I have made much more like a native speaker. I would appreciate it if you could help me. The sentences here are the answer about the first class. The first phase is about my hometown, the second is about my name, the third is about my job, and last but not least is about my electronic devices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-17/</guid>
      <description>Thanks, Anj. I love your class, you are full of passion and patience. You are an excellent and professional teacher. , I think you have magic in the class. When I take your class, you can take all of my attention. I think you are very popular on this platform, your class is very hard to reserve.
I have worked from home since two months ago.
engoo.com/en/materials</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-18/</guid>
      <description>18th May 2022 Yesterday, I am sorry heard you External Solid State Drive is corrupted. Is name correct, or Mobile Solid State Storage, or external hard driver, which one is usual. SSD, the short name is often used in China, so do Philippine? I remember that you bought it from Shopee. It&amp;rsquo;s may be a China brand.
The electronic device in Chinese brand I only suggest HUAWEI, XIAOMI, VIVO, HONOR, and Lenovo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airren.github.io/English-learning/2022-05-19/</guid>
      <description>Today，Let&amp;rsquo;s talk something about computer
All the computers that are developed are not the same, they have different designs and features. Some computers have a very high capacity as well as working speed; however, some are slow. Depending on the requirements, computers are being developed.
Depending upon the internal structure, and applicability, the computer system is categorized as follows −
Mainframe Computer It is high capacity and costly computer. It is largely used by big organizations where many people can use it simultaneously.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
